Guide to the Freewater Production Films and Records, 1967-2003 and undated UA.09.13.0005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Freewater Productions Films: 1996, 71 items
  - The Sandwich (1996)
    - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 5 of 5, 150 ft. (Box 26)
      From container: Work Print Edits, Scratch, and Color
    - Positive Print, 16mm, sd., co., reel 1 of 1, 400 ft. (Box 26)
      From container: Grant Film.
  - [Freewater Productions Films Workshop Reel] (1996)
    - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 160 ft. (Box 27)
      From container: Work Print CR.
  - Hal Kammerer Award Submissions, 1995-1996 (1996)
    - VHS, 120 min. (Box 37)
- Freewater Productions Films: 1997, 14 items
  Contains films made in 1997.
  - Endless Love (1997)
    Directed by Patrick Wacker.
    - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 2, 775 ft. (Box 27)
    - Negative, 16mm, reel 2 of 2, 550 ft. (Box 27)
    - Betacam SP, 30 min. (Box 36)
      From container: Sound only.
    - Betacam SP, 30 min. (Box 37)
      From container: Working Copy.
  - Looking for Elysian Street (1997)
    Directed by Michael Bott. Starring Jordan Sadle.
    - Positive Print, 16mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1, 180 ft. (Box 27)
  - Stoplight (1997)
    - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 900 ft. (Box 27)
      From container: Original Camera Negative.
      Edge Number Registers and Camera Reports moved to Documentation series.
    - Betacam SP, 30 min. (Box 36)
      From container: Sound for Stoplight Scene 1.
    - DAT, 60 min. (Box 36)
  - Suggs Must Die! (1997)
    Directed by Roger Beebe. 1998 Kammerer Award winner.
    - Positive Print, 16mm, sd., co., reel 1 of 1, 450 ft. (Box 27)
      From film: Heads A/B Roll.
    - MiniDV, 11 min. (Box 36)
      Tape is entitled: Roger Beebe's Freewater Films (Plus Two). Tape also includes: Eat Art, A Fragmentary History of the 21st Century, Dirty Harry and the Hendersons, What Boys Want.
    - VHS, 11 min. (Box 38)
  - Untitled (1997)
    Directed by Ray Wyant and Carl Kingsford.
    - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 2, 440 ft. (Box 27)
    - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 2 of 2, 440 ft. (Box 27)
  - Untitled (1997)
    - Reversal Original, 16mm, si., co., reel 1 of 1, 460 ft. (Box 27)
      From film: Filter Test Roll.
- Freewater Productions Films: 1998, 2 items
  Contains films made in 1998.
  - What Boys Want (1998)
    - MiniDV, 60 min. (Box 36)
      Tape is entitled: Roger Beebe's Freewater Films (Plus Two). Tape also includes: Eat Art, A Fragmentary History of the 21st Century, Dirty Harry and the Hendersons, Suggs Must Die!
  - Hal Kammerer Award Submissions (1998)
    - VHS, 120 min. (Box 38)
- Freewater Productions Films: 1999, 24 items
  Contains films made in 1999.
  - A Fragmentary History of the 21st Century (1999)
    - MiniDV, 19 min. (Box 36)
      Tape is entitled: Roger Beebe's Freewater Films (Plus Two). Tape also includes: Suggs Must Die!, Dirty Harry and the Hendersons, Eat Art, What Boys Want.
    - VHS, 19 min. (Box 38)
  - Bloom (1999)
    Directed by Margaret Chapman.
    - Negative, 16mm, reels 1-8 of 8, 800 ft. (Box 28)
      From container: Negative W/P and Dartmouth College Film Stories, Process Normal.
      Photocopy of original cover of reel 8 in Documentation series.
  - Me, Myself, and Eye (1999)
    Directed by Benjamin Epps.
    - VHS, tape 1 of 2, 26 min. (Box 38)
    - VHS, tape 2 of 2, 26 min. (Box 36)
      Tape also includes: Phil Armonik, And the Bunnies Shall Rule, Pig Without A Cue.
  - Visions of a Call (1999)
    Directed by Shani Harris.
    - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 2, 300 ft. (Box 28)
      From container: A-roll Original Camera Negative.
      Lab Effects Sheet and Timing Sheets moved to Documentation series.
    - Negative, 16mm, reel 2 of 2, 280 ft. (Box 28)
      From container: B-roll Original Camera Negative.
    - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 1 of 2, 300 ft. (Box 28)
    - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 2 of 2, 70 ft. (Box 28)
    - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 260 ft. (Box 28)
      From container: Magnetic Stock.
    - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 260 ft. (Box 28)
  - Hal Kammerer Award Submissions (1999)
    - VHS, 120 min. (Box 38)
  - Untitled (1999)
    Directed by Margaret Chapman. Magnetic Stock footage.
    - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 1 of 6, 275 ft. (Box 28)
    - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reels 2-6 of 6, 350 ft. (Box 28)
      From container: Heads/Tails, Tone, Outtakes.
  - Untitled (1999)
    - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 950 ft. (Box 28)
- Freewater Productions Films: 2000, 9 items
  Contains films made in 2000.
  - A Conversation with Herbert Simon (2000)
    Directed by Julia Love. Kammerer Award submission.
    - VHS, 26 min. (Box 38)
  - Bridled! (2000)
    Directed by Alanna Thain.
    - VHS, tape 1 of 2, 120 min. (Box 37)
    - VHS, tape 2 of 2, 120 min. (Box 38)
  - Damn Sacred (2000)
    Directed by Paul Fleschner.
    - VHS, 10 min. (Box 37)
  - Hare Krishna: The Misunderstood Faith (2000)
    Directed by Rob Moody. Kammerer Award submission.
    - VHS, 6 min. (Box 38)
  - News Correspondence (2000)
    Directed by Jason Middleton.
    - VHS, 4 min. (Box 38)
  - Phil Armonik (2000)
    Directed by Benjamin Epps. Featuring Clay Taliaferro. Music by Antony John.
    - VHS, tapes 1-2 of 2, 44 min. (Box 37)
      Two identical copies present.
    - VHS, 22 min. (Box 37)
      Tape also includes: And the Bunnies Shall Rule, Pig Without A Cue, Me, Myself, and Eye.
  - Hal Kammerer Award Submissions (2000)
    - VHS, 120 min. (Box 38)
      Tape includes: Phil Armonik, Me, Myself, and Eye, Hare Krishna, A Conversation with Herbert Simon. Four identical copies present.
      Contents list moved to Documentation series.
- Freewater Productions Films: 2001, 18 items
  Contains films made in 2001.
  - A Better Place (2001)
    Directed by Jesse Eisenhardt. From container: Copyright Snake & Crane Productions.
    - MiniDV, 60 min. (Box 36)
      Editing instructions moved to Documentation series.
  - A Letter (Reflections on Memory, Movement, and Bicycles) (2001)
    - DVCAM, 7 min. (Box 36)
      Tape also includes: Prelude to Matrimony, Markheim. From container: Master.
    - DVCAM, 7 min. (Box 36)
    - VHS, 7 min. (Box 37)
      Tape also includes: Prelude to Matrimony, Markheim. From container: Dubbed from DVCAM master.
    - VHS, 7 min. (Box 37)
  - Elevator Music (2001)
    Directed by Russell Robinson and Nic de Armendi.
    - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 400 ft. (Box 29)
      From container: Work Print. Reel also includes: Study Skills.
  - Seattle Symphony (Or, How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Coffee) (2001)
    Directed by Isham Randolph. Kammerer Award submission.
    - VHS, 120 min. (Box 38)
  - Signal Transduction (2001)
    Directed by Jason Middleton. Kammerer Award submission.
    - Negative, 16mm, b&w, reel 1 of 2, 350 ft. (Box 29)
      From container: Original Negative, A-Roll.
    - Negative, 16mm, b&w, reel 2 of 2, 300 ft. (Box 29)
      From container: Original Negative, B-Roll.
    - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 250 ft. (Box 29)
      From container: Soundtrack.
    - Optical Sound, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 325 ft. (Box 29)
    - Positive Print, 16mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1, 200 ft. (Box 29)
    - Positive Print, 16mm, b&w, reel 1 of 1, 300 ft. (Box 29)
    - VHS, 7 min. (Box 38)
  - Study Skills (2001)
    - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 400 ft. (Box 29)
      From container: Work Print. Reel also includes: Elevator Music.
      Miscellaneous paperwork moved to Documentation series.
  - The Grail (2001)
    Directed by Kurt Volkan.
    - VHS, 120 min. (Box 38)
  - When I Grow Up: Stories from the People on the Bus (2001)
    Directed by Sarah Chasnovitz and Peter Jordan.
    - VHS, 35 min. (Box 38)
  - Hal Kammerer Award Submissions (2001)
    - VHS, 120 min. (Box 38)
      Tape includes: Aria, The Grail, Bridled!, Signal Transduction, News Correspondence, Seattle Symphony, A Better Place, When I Grow Up.
- Freewater Productions Films: 2002, 9 items
  Contains films made in 2002.
  - Chance of a Lifetime (2002)
    Directed by Nayeli Garie-Crupo.
    - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 300 ft. (Box 29)
      Negative Report moved to Documentation series.
  - Hyperman (2002)
    Directed by Russell Robinson.
    - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 1000 ft. (Box 29)
      Edge Number Report and Camera Reports moved to Documentation series.
    - DAT, 94 min. (Box 36)
  - Markheim (2002)
    Directed by Sam Morgan.
    - DVCAM, 32 min. (Box 36)
      Tape also includes: Prelude to Matrimony, A Letter. From container: Master.
    - VHS, 32 min. (Box 36)
      Tape also includes: Prelude to Matrimony, A Letter. From container: Dubbed from DVCAM Master.
  - Prelude to Matrimony (2002)
    Directed by Shani Harris Peterson.
    - Negative, 16mm, b&w, reel 1 of 1, 400 ft. (Box 29)
      Tape also includes: Markheim, A Letter.
    - DVCAM, 16 min. (Box 36)
    - VHS, 16 min. (Box 37)
      Tape also includes: Markheim, A Letter. From container: Dubbed from DVCAM Master.
    - VHS, 16 min. (Box 36)
- Freewater Productions Films: 2003, 14 items
  Contains films made in 2003.
  - Antonia's Tony (2003)
    Directed by Matt Simon, Lauren Wolkstein.
    - DVD-R, 10 min. (Box 36)
  - Harder (2003)
    Directed by Gabe Morgan.
    - DVCAM, 13 min. (Box 36)
      Tape also includes: Mine.
    - VHS, 13 min. (Box 37)
    - VHS, 13 min. (Box 37)
  - Light Tonight (2003)
    Directed by Hillary Kaylor and Matt Signer.
    - DVCAM, 13 min. (Box 36)
      From container: Master.
    - MiniDV, 13 min. (Box 36)
    - VHS, 13 min. (Box 36)
      From container: Dub from DVCAM Master.
  - Mine (2003)
    Directed by Carrie Schrader.
    - DVCAM, 7 min. (Box 36)
      Tape also includes: Harder.
    - MiniDV, 7 min. (Box 36)
      Tape also includes: Light Tonight.
    - VHS, 7 min. (Box 36)
  - Miranda Rights (2003)
    Directed by Elan Dassani.
    - MiniDV, 21 min. (Box 36)
  - Harder (2003)
    - VHS, 13 min. (Box 36)
  - Prague Spring (2003)
    - VHS, 120 min. (Box 37)
  - The Grim Rhymer (2003)
    - VHS, 13 min. (Box 37)
- Freewater Productions Films: Undated, 83 items
  Contains undated films. Series is divided into Titled and Untitled subseries.
  - Titled and Undated Films (2003)
    Includes films for which there is a title or brief summary available, but no date.
    - [African-American Church Service]
      - Negative, 16mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 2, 1200 ft. (Box 30)
      - Negative, 16mm, si., b&w, reel 2 of 2, 1200 ft. (Box 30)
    - A Guitar Documentary
      Directed by Douglas Scott.
      - Negative, 16mm si., b&w, reel 1 of 1, 240 ft. (Box 30)
    - An Eternity Away
      Directed by Xavier Márquez.
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 2, 500 ft. (Box 30)
        From container: Work Prints.
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 2 of 2, 950 ft. (Box 30)
    - And the Bunnies Shall Rule
      - VHS, 1 min. (Box 37)
        Tape also includes: Phil Armonik, Pig Without A Cue, Me, Myself, and Eye.
    - [Animation Trailer]
      - Positive Print, 16mm, sd., co., reel 1 of 1, 300 ft. (Box 30)
    - Bill Bean
      Directed by Gerhart and Jensen.
      - DAT, 100 min. (Box 36)
    - Billie
      Directed by Mark Korman.
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 200 ft. (Box 31)
        From container: Finished Work Print.
    - Body Movement
      - Negative, 16mm, sd., reel 1 of 1, 200 ft. (Box 32)
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 180 ft. (Box 32)
      - 3/4-inch Umatic, 30 min. (Box 37)
        From container: Dirty Dupe, Color Transfer without sound or burn-in window.
    - Dirty Harry and the Hendersons
      - MiniDV, 60 min. (Box 36)
        Tape is entitled: Roger Beebe's Freewater Films (Plus Two). Tape also includes: Suggs Must Die!, A Fragmentary History of the 21st Century, Eat Art, What Boys Want.
    - Duke University Union Promo
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 130 ft. (Box 32)
        From container: Reel No. 3, Original ECN.
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 2, 1000 ft. (Box 32)
        From container: Original Negative, A and B-Rolls.
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 2 of 2, 800 ft. (Box 32)
      - Positive Print, 16mm, co., reels 1-3 of 3, 140 ft. (Box 32)
        Contains 3 reels, 90 ft., 40 ft., 15 ft.
    - Ecos
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 700 ft. (Box 31)
    - Ed Morrow
      - Negative, 16mm, sd., co., reel 1 of 1, 700 ft. (Box 31)
        From container: Orig. Pix R-1, Color with Magnetic Soundtrack.
    - Experiment in Creativity
      Synopsis from film: The filmed sequences you are about to see were taken during the course of an eight-week pilot project conceived by two Durham women, ex-teachers, who felt the necessity both to increase community involvement in public education, and to seriously open for consideration the necessity of making education in creative skills a primary aspect of elementary education. The Education Committee of the First Presbyterian Church of Durham, itself having been at work on the concept of arts education, sponsored the pilot project.
      - Negative, 16mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1, 425 ft. (Box 32)
    - Faculty Flick
      Directed by Parker, Osbourne, Wilder and Fowlie.
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 5, 840 ft. (Box 31)
      - Negative, 16mm, reels 2-5 of 5, 1825 ft. (Box 31)
      - Negative, 16mm, Positive Print, 16mm, reels 1-5 of 5, 2000 ft. (Box 31)
        From container: Negatives and Work Prints.
    - Fifty Dollars
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 180 ft. (Box 32)
    - [Footage of Downtown Durham]
      From container: Looks like another documentary, this one contrasting blacks and whites, poor and rich, Durham and Duke.
      - Positive Print, 16mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1, 220 ft. (Box 31)
    - [Footage of Duke Gardens]
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 140 ft. (Box 34)
    - [Footage of Ocean]
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 140 ft. (Box 33)
    - Fortunes
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 2, 400 ft. (Box 32)
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 2 of 2, 170 ft. (Box 32)
    - Foulie
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 4, 400 ft. (Box 32)
      - Negative, 16mm, reels 2-3 of 4, 700 ft. (Box 32)
        Can has 2 reels, 600 ft. and 100 ft.
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 4 of 4, 800 ft. (Box 32)
        From film: Head.
    - [Freewater Productions Films Logo Designs]
      - Negative, 16mm, si., b&w, reels 1-2 of 2, 140 ft. (Box 32)
        Can has 2 reels, 120 ft., 20 ft.
      - Reversal Original, 16mm, si., co., reels 1-2 of 2, 80 ft. (Box 32)
        Can has 2 reels, 70 ft., 10 ft.
    - [Freewater Productions Films Workshop Reel]
      - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 780 ft. (Box 34)
    - Frelon
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 600 ft. (Box 32)
    - Garibaldi
      - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 125 ft. (Box 32)
    - [Gerhart's Retirement Party Footage]
      - Betacam SP, 15 min. (Box 37)
        From container: Edit Master.
    - Golden Echoes
      - Negative, 16mm, co., reel 1 of 2, 850 ft. (Box 30)
        From container: Processed Original Negative and Anthro Film.
      - Negative, 16mm, co., reel 2 of 2, 1150 ft. (Box 30)
        From container: Processed Original Negative.
      - Positive Print, 16mm, sd., reel 1 of 1, 950 ft. (Box 30)
        From container: Work Print of first shooting, Resolved Sound.
    - Hal Kammerer Award Submissions
      - VHS, 120 min. (Box 37)
    - Les Couteaux
      - Positive Print, 16mm, sd., co., reel 1 of 1, 260 ft. (Box 32)
    - Mayday
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 1250 ft. (Box 33)
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 140 ft. (Box 33)
    - [Music Video]
      - Positive Print, 16mm, b&w, reel 1 of 1, 420 ft. (Box 33)
        From container: Work Print, No Sound Found.
    - Pig Without a Cue
      - VHS, 7 min. (Box 37)
        Tape also includes: Phil Armonik, And the Bunnies Shall Rule, Me, Myself, and Eye.
    - Puzzles
      - VHS, 120 min. (Box 38)
    - Science Experiment
      Directed by Vivian Casagrarde.
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 4, 650 ft. (Box 34)
        From container: Original Negatives.
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 2 of 4, 120 ft. (Box 34)
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 3 of 4, 150 ft. (Box 34)
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 4 of 4, 400 ft. (Box 34)
    - The Miracle Drug
      - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 200 ft. (Box 34)
    - The Persistence of Vision
      Directed by Michael Cato.
      - VHS, 120 ft. (Box 38)
    - The Sacrificial King: A Reading
      Directed by Margaret McCarthy. From container: Duke Institute of the Arts.
      - VHS, 120 min. (Box 38)
    - [Sunflower]
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 80 ft. (Box 34)
    - WXDU Trailer
      - Betacam SP, 2 min. (Box 36)
        Tape also includes: Round Two, Dying, The Tale of Quasi-Hobo, Duke University Union Promo, Passage, The One I Love, Anti-War Demonstration.
    - Yearbook
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 140 ft. (Box 31)
    - Yearlook Ad
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 100 ft. (Box 34)
  - Untitled and Undated Films
    Contains films lacking both a title and a date.
    - Untitled
      - Reversal Original, Super 8mm, reel 1 of 1, 120 ft. (Box 33)
    - Untitled
      - Betacam SP, 30 min. (Box 37)
        From container: Betsy's Footage.
        Document Listing Time and Key Codes moved to Documentation series.
    - Untitled
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 820 ft. (Box 34)
    - Untitled
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 130 ft. (Box 29)
        From container: Betsy Frederick.
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 130 ft. (Box 29)
    - Untitled
      - Positive Print, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 260 ft. (Box 35)
    - Untitled
      Directed by Steven Wright.
      - VHS, 30 min. (Box 38)
    - Untitled
      - Reversal Original, 16mm, si., b&w, reel 1 of 1, 200 ft. (Box 33)
        Includes shots of forest, car, the First Last Handy Mart, and guitar player.
    - Untitled
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 100 ft. (Box 33)
        From container: ECN and Keith Project.
    - Untitled
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 450 ft. (Box 33)
        From container: Black Leader.
    - Untitled
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 2, 720 ft. (Box 33)
        From container: A-B Roll.
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 2 of 2, 1100 ft. (Box 33)
    - Untitled
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 60 ft. (Box 33)
    - Untitled
      - Negative, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 280 ft. (Box 35)
    - Untitled
      - Negative, 16mm, reels 1-2 of 1, 380 ft. (Box 33)
        From container: Original Negative, N.T.
    - Untitled
      - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 80 ft. (Box 35)
    - Untitled
      - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 650 ft. (Box 35)
        From container: Ins.
    - Untitled
      - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 1 of 1, 280 ft. (Box 35)
    - Untitled
      - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 1 of 2, 420 ft. (Box 34)
        Includes 21 reels of varying sizes. From container: Sound Effects: wooshes, whistles, crowd roar, seal screams, and others.
      - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 2 of 2, 700 ft. (Box 34)
        Includes 9 reels of varying sizes. From container: school bells, applause in stadium, people laughing, tin cans rattling, freaky synths, roller coaster, and others.
        Sheets with labels moved to Documentation series.
    - Untitled
      From container: Uncut Sound.
      - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 1 of 2, 900 ft. (Box 35)
      - Magnetic Sound, 16mm, reel 2 of 2, 900 ft. (Box 35)
    - Untitled
      From film: Performed by Gladys Bailin, Michael Ballard, Caroline Carlson, Anne Ditson, Raymond Johnson, Murray Louis, Marcia Wardel. Includes shots of modern and ballet dancers onstage, ballet dancers outdoors, students playing in snow, and belly dancer.
      - Positive Print, 16mm, sd., co., reel 1 of 1, 280 ft. (Box 35)
- Freewater Productions Films: Oversized Materials (1986, 1992), 3 items
  Contains oversize film reels removed from previous series.
  - Oblivion: A Science Fiction Adventure (1986), 1200 ft.
    Directed by Dave Pratt, Fred Stein, and Jim LeClair. From film: Big Blue Ashtray Productions presents…
    - Positive Print, 16mm, sd., co., reel 1 of 1 (Box 39)
  - The Happy Stone (1992)
    - Positive Print, 16mm, sd., co., reel 1 of 1, 900 ft. (Box 39)
      From film: A-Roll.
- Freewater Productions Films: Documentation (1979-2003 and undated), 1 box
  Contains paper documentation removed from previous series.
  - 1979 Films
    - The Lost Last Reel of the Birth of a Nation: Explanatory Page (Box 40)
  - 1985 Films
    - Dusk: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
    - The Fuse: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
    - Untitled: Edge Number Register, 2 folders (Box 40)
  - 1986 Films
    - Dreamwalker: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
  - 1988 Films
    - Academics Now: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
    - The Interview: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
    - The Significant Other: Edge Number Register and Mixing Cue Sheet, 3 folders (Box 40)
  - 1989 Films
    - [Duke University Union Promo]: Cue Sheet (Box 40)
    - Old Man: Magnetic Sound, Mixing Instructions (Box 40)
    - Perchance to Dream: Positive Print, Director's Notes on Splicing (Box 40)
    - Untitled [Directed by Robeson]: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
    - Untitled: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
  - 1990 Films
    - Devil's Quarters: Edge Number Register and Instruction Sheet (Box 40)
      (2 folders)
    - Duke University Union Promo: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
    - [Klink]: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
  - 1991 Films
    - Pizza King: Edge Number Registers and Timing Charts (Box 40)
    - Duke University Union Promo: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
  - 1992 Films
    - Ceci N'est Pas un Film: Edge Number Registers and Timing Charts (Box 40)
    - Duke University Union Promo: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
    - The Happy Stone: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
    - Yearbook: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
    - Untitled [Directed by Xavier Marquez]: Photocopy of original box cover (Box 40)
  - 1993 Films
    - Mah at the Hideway: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
    - The Legend of Herring (Reels 1-4 of 4): Edge Number Registers (Box 40)
    - The Legend of Herring (Reels 1-6 of 6): Edge Number Registers (Box 40)
    - Untitled [From container: Kate and Seth Practice]: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
  - 1994 Films
    - Duke University Union Promo: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
    - Rock-A-Bye, Bye Baby: Edge Number Registers (Box 40)
    - Untitled [Directed by Justin Lester]: Edge Number Registers (Box 40)
    - Untitled: Edge Number Registers (Box 40)
  - 1995 Films
    - Cable 13: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
    - Duet/Biology: Edge Number Registers (Box 40)
    - The Fortune Teller: Edge Number Registers (Box 40)
    - Toaster: Edge Number Registers (Box 40)
  - 1996 Films
    - A-I: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
    - Another Day, Another Dollar: Edge Receipts (Box 40)
    - A Short Film About Killing: Edge Number Registers (Box 40)
    - Cinderella's Shoe: Edge Number Registers (Box 40)
    - Missing Peace: Edge Number Registers (Box 40)
    - Richard Krauss: Work Order (Box 40)
    - The Sandwich: Edge Number Registers, Camera Reports, Credits Posters (Box 40)
      (2 folders).
  - 1997 Films
    - Endless Love: Edge Number Register (Box 40)
    - Stoplight: Edge Number Registers, Camera Reports (Box 40)
  - 1999 Films
    - Bloom [reel 8 of 8]: Photocopy of original cover (Box 40)
    - Visions of a Call: Lab Effects Sheet, Timing Sheet (Box 40)
  - 2001 Films
    - A Better Place: Editing Instructions (Box 40)
    - Signal Transduction: Cue Sheet (Box 40)
    - Study Skills: Positive Print, miscellaneous paperwork (Box 40)
  - 2002 Films
    - Chance of a Lifetime: Negative Report (Box 40)
    - Hyperman: Edge Number Report, Camera Report (Box 40)
  - Undated Films
    - Untitled [Directed by Betsy Frederick]: Document Listing Times, Key Codes (Box 40)
    - Untitled [Sound Effects, reels 1-21 of 21]: Label Sheets (Box 40)